我在 2012 年六月加入了馬圈。
我不知道這將
塑造我接下來的人生。
這是我敬圈子的一首歌。
敬友誼公主。
公主，親愛的
Dear Princess
你是否在那？
Are you there?
我一直在等
I've been waiting
等你來這兒
waiting for you here
一個新的世界，時機已到
The time has come for a new world
別在過去中迴轉
Don't wander in the past
不曾知我已準備
Never knew that I was ready
它來的好快
It came on so fast
你造就一富城
You've made a kingdom
它會持續到時間盡頭
that will last until the end of time
我將回報你的教養
To tell you that you've raised me high
在這封信裡頭
in my letter to you
從此岸到彼岸
From sea to shining sea
我們乘著回憶
we carry memories
從世界各地
from everywhere
每個物種都按時
Everycreature knows their time
公主，親愛的
Dear Princess
時機已到
the time has come
你該走了
for you to go
戰局已勝
The battle's won
公主，求你幫我擦乾眼淚
Princess, please wipe these tears from my eyes
我不知我能否放手
I don't know if I can let go
我所知道的一切
Everything I've ever known
都是你所教
came from you
公主，我求你
So Princess, please
我不想離去
I don't want to go
我學了好多
I've learned so much
我會傳承直到永恆
I'll carry it all forever
公主，親愛的
Dear Princess
我們會盡全力
We'll try our best
帶著你所教一切
To take what you've taught us
一個偉大旅程
A great new quest
即使我們跌倒
Though we may fall
只要飛越天空
Fly through the air
我們永遠會記得
We'll always remember
彼此間的魔法
The magic we shared
這僅僅是一個新世紀的開始。
別害怕。
特別感謝大家為了最後一段歌詞
所貢獻的歌聲。這個圈子的大家
才是這個圈子的特殊。